&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：因为之前有人问过，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Since it was asked earlier,
让我们进入对const的讨论。
let's segue into a discussion of const.
按大多数人的说法，const甚至比let更好。
Const is by most accounts even better than let.
您甚至不应该使用let，并且应该在可能的情况下只使用const。
You should not even use let and you should only use const wherever possible.
因此，const的问题实质上是const关键字
So the problem that I have with const is essentially the const keyword
在语言中没有自己的分量。
does not carry its own weight within the language.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这是一个有时用于规范或
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That's a phrase that is sometimes used in specifications or
标准。
standards.
当有人说，是的，可能会有好处，但是
When somebody says, yeah, there might be a benefit, but
成本更高，所以不值得。
the cost is greater and so it's not worth it.
我想说的是，Const可能会有一点好处，
And what I'm saying is, that there might be a slight benefit to const,
它并不像你被引导去相信的那样重要，而且
it is not as significant as you have been led to believe, and
在我看来，const的成本更高。
there is a cost to const which is in my opinion greater.
它没有自己的重量。
It doesn't carry its own weight.
这并不意味着我从来不用它，它意味着我在使用它的时候非常节省
That doesn't mean I never use it, it means I am very sparing in when I use it and
我只在非常特殊的情况下使用它。
I only use it in very specific cases.
与之相反，它是我对所有声明的一般替代。
As opposed to it's my general replacement for all declarations.
因此，const带来的巨大成本甚至不是JavaScript独有的。
So, the big cost that comes with const is not even unique to JavaScript.
如果您现在继续Stack Overflow并搜索
If you go on Stack Overflow right now and search for
const关键字的问题，您会发现数以万计的
problems with the const keyword, you'll find tens of thousands of
跨越各种不同语言的帖子。
posts across a whole variety of different languages.
因为事实证明，每次将const关键字添加到任何
Because it turns out, every time the const keyword has ever been added to any
编程语言，程序员被弄糊涂了。
programming language, programmers got confused.
我认为他们感到困惑的原因之一是，
And I think one of the reasons they get confused,
是因为当我们想到const，我们想到单词const。
is because when we think of const, and we think of the word constant.
我们在想的是，一件不会改变的事情。
What we're thinking to ourselves is, a thing that doesn't change.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：但这不是程序员所说的const，或者
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: But that's not what a programmer means by const, or
至少这不是编程语言设计者对const的意思。
at least that's not what a programming language designer means by const.
编程语言设计器意味着不能重新分配的变量，
A programming language designer means a variable that can't be reassigned,
这是两件完全不同的事情。
and those are two entirely different things.
在这里，在第4行，我声明了一个const，一个不能重新分配的myTeacher。
Here, on line 4, am declaring a const, a myTeacher that can't be reassigned.
所以我在第5行得到一个错误，但是
So I get an error on line 5, but
看看当我像数组一样声明一个可变的值时会发生什么。
look what happens when I declare a mutable value like an array.
我没有试图重新分配8号线上的老师，所以我没有错误，
I'm not trying to reassign teachers on line 8, so I get no error,
但实际上我仍然在变异完全被允许的值。
but I am actually still mutating the value which is totally allowed.
这就造成了各种各样的挫折感，事实上，
This creates all kinds of frustration, as a matter of fact,
有些语言在这方面做了很大的努力。
some languages have struggled so much with this.
就像Java一样，它们移到const关键字并
Like for example Java, they removed to the const keyword and
输入另一个称为final的关键字。
put in another keyword called final.
这样他们就可以把自己从人们的包袱中分离出来
Just so they could sort of separate themselves from the baggage of people
认为这件事意味着一些它没有的东西。
thinking that this thing meant something that it didn't.
我不确定决赛是不是更好，但他们就是这么做的，好吗？
I'm not sure that final is better, but that's what they did, okay?
因此，Const随之而来的是一个行李。
So, there is a baggage that comes with const.
和一个新的代码阅读器，除非他们已经非常熟悉
And a new reader to your code unless they are already well familiar with
常量的概念，以及可变的值和
the concept of const, and the idea of the difference between mutable values and
可变分配。
mutable assignments.
当读者看到你说的话时，很有可能会被绊倒
It is more likely than not that a reader could get tripped up when they see you say
常数教师等于，然后他们看到类似数组的东西，
const teachers equals and then they see something like an array,
它们最有可能是他们将得到的外卖或
they are most likely takeaway that they would get or
他们最有可能得到的印象是数组不会改变。
the most likely impression that they would get is that the array won't change.
它不会自己变异，这不是你想说的。
That it won't mutate itself, that's not what you were saying.
你说，不，我只是不会重新分配变量，
You were saying, no, I'm just not gonna reassign the variable,
所以当你突变数组时，它们突然变得混乱。
so that when you mutate the array, all of a sudden they get confused.
所以const关键字有这个问题，它有这个包袱。
So the const keyword has this problem to it, it has this baggage.
现在，您应该在一个非常小的块中使用const关键字，对吗？
Now, you're supposed to use the const keyword within a very small block, right?
你应该保持你的街区小
You're supposed to keep your block small and
应该在小块内使用const关键字。
you're supposed to use the const key word within small blocks.
从语义的角度来看，const关键字实际上所说的是，
What the const keyword is actually saying, from a semantic perspective is,
对于这个街区的其余部分，我保证它不会被重新分配。
for the rest of this block, I promise it's not gonna get reassigned.
我不认为调职真的是个大问题。
I don't think that reassignment is actually a big problem.
这不是我的程序中典型的bug来源。
That isn't the source of bugs typically in my program.
但即使它是bug的来源，如果我使用一小块
But even if it were a source of bugs, if I use the const inside of a small block of
三到五行代码，我最多告诉用户的是，你猜怎么着，
three to five lines of code, what I am at best telling the user is, guess what,
在接下来的四行代码中，我不会重新分配它。
on the next four lines of code I'm not gonna reassign it.
因为在整个程序中只有四行代码可以重新分配
Cuz there is only four more lines of code in the entire program that could reassign
由于词法作用域的工作方式，&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：const关键字
it, because of how lexical scoping works, &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The const keyword
假装它在为我们做一件很棒的事情，而且
pretends as if it's doing this major awesome thing for us, and
它实际上并没有做那么多。
it's not actually doing that much at all.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：没有解决那么多问题。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Not solving that many problems.
所以它有这样的问题，它并没有真正解决这个问题
So it has this problems, and it's not really solving the problem that
它假装，有点像你孩子卧室里的夜灯。
it pretends, it's kinda like a night lighting in your child's bedroom.
壁橱里没有怪物肯定会让你的孩子感觉更好，
It definitely makes your child feel better that there's no monsters in the closet,
但我们都知道壁橱里没有怪物。
but we all know there's no monsters in the closet.
所以它让你感觉很好，但我不确定它是否真的带着
So it makes you feel good, but I'm not sure that it really is carrying its
自己的体重和潜在的困惑来了。
own weight with the potential of confusion that comes.
所以，所有这些都考虑在内，我个人对const的看法是，我
So, all of that taken into consideration, my personal take on const is that I
仅当我分配一个已经是原语的值时才使用它，并且
only use it when I am assigning a value that is already a primitive and
因此是不变的。
therefore immutable.
因此，我只会将const与字符串、布尔值或数字一起使用。
So I will only use const with things like strings, Booleans, or numbers.
我使用它作为这些文字的语义占位符。
And I use it as a semantic place holder for those literals.
所以如果有数字13，这意味着一些特别的东西
So if have the number 13, and that means something special and
Magical在我的程序中，我会给它命名为Special Magical in a Const
magical in my program, I'll give it the name special magical in a const
声明而不是只使用13。
declaration instead of just using 13.
这就是常量的作用。
That's what constants are supposed to be for.
它们应该作为占位符给出语义含义。
They're supposed to give semantic meaning as placeholders.
我不认为我们需要一个常量来防止我们意外地重新分配东西。
I don't think we need a const to prevent us from accidentally reassigning things.
我只是不认为这是一个很大的问题，至少在一般意义上是这样。
I just don't think it's that big of a problem, at least in the general sense.
这是我对const的看法，在那里许多开发人员
That's my take on const, where many of the developers
外面会告诉你应该使用const。
out there will tell you that you should use const.
然后你应该使用let，永远不要使用var。
And then you should use let and you should never use var.
我的建议是相反的，你应该默认使用var。
My advice is reversed, you should default to using var.
在有帮助的地方使用let，
Use let where it is helpful,
仅对不可变的原始值谨慎地使用const。
use const sparingly only with immutable primitive values.